Finding Aid for Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee Publications, 1958-1963
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee Publications 1958-1963
Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee
0.2 linear ft.
FN 4 H967 P976
Publications of the Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee, mainly Watershed news publications as well as annual reports.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group is open without restriction.
The Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee, comprised of various cities and townships in Southeastern Michigan, was established in 1958 to "sponsor studies of water problems" in the area (HRWIC, first annual report, p.2). In 1965, the Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee became the Huron River Watershed Council.
The collection consists of various publications of the Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee, mainly Watershed news publications as well as annual reports. Publications from 1965 and later are in the Huron River Watershed Council publication collection.
Subjects:
Huron River (Oakland County-Monroe County, Mich.); Huron River Watershed (Oakland County-Monroe County, Mich.); Regional planning--Michigan, Southeastern.; Water-supply--Michigan, Southeastern.; Water conservation--Michigan, Southeastern.; Huron River Watershed Intergovernmental Committee.
- Serials
  - Annual reports (Box 1)
    - 1958/1959 (Box 1)
    - 1958/1960 (Box 1)
    - 1960/1961 (Box 1)
    - 1961/1962 (Box 1)
- Non-serial publications
  - 1958
    - Water management in the Huron River basin, by Norman Billings (Box 1)
      (Watershed news, no.1)
  - 1959
    - The problem of coordination in watershed management: a case study of the Huron River basin, by Sanford Farness (Box 1)
      (Watershed news, no.2)
    - Water, the key to the areas' future: a series of seven articles published in the Ann Arbor news, by Roger Paton (Box 1)
      (Watershed news, no.3)
    - Community cooperation in water management in the Huron basin, by William Gable (Box 1)
      (Watershed news, no.4)
  - 1960
    - The Huron River: a water use policy and development program (Box 1)
    - Changing land use patterns, by Charles R. Kaufman (Box 1)
      (Watershed news )
  - 1963
    - Organization for water planning and management of the Huron River. Rev. June 1963 (Box 1)
    - The need for water legislation in Michigan, by Lyle E. Craine (Box 1)
      (Watershed news, no.8)
    - The Huron River watershed: a water use policy and development program. (Box 1)
      (Reprinted August 1963)
    - The importance of the management of the Huron River watershed: conference proceedings (Box 1)